hi everybody I'm glad to see you to see
大家好，我很高兴见到你
all of you here and right now I'd like
大家都在这里，现在我想
to share some some details some short
分享一些细节
talk about completable future a little
谈论可完成的未来
bit details about that slide probably a
关于幻灯片的一些细节可能是
lot of already familiar with that slide
很多已经熟悉的幻灯片
but I in anyway I have to put it I like
但无论如何我都必须说出我喜欢的
that's like really and if our company
就像真的，如果我们的公司
didn't have such cute lawyers I would
我没有那么可爱的律师
ask them to do that because this slide
请他们这样做，因为这张幻灯片
is my savings
是我的积蓄
I could bring total crap from from the
我可以从
stage and this means I'm not responsible
阶段，这意味着我不负责任
for that
为了那个原因
okay a couple words about me I'm working
好吧，关于我的几句话我在工作
in Oracle and my goal in Oracle my job
在Oracle中的工作以及我在Oracle中的目标
at Oracle to make GDK Java Java Virtual
甲骨文公司将GDK Java Java虚拟化
Machine faster I am a performance
机速我是一个表现
engineer so I have to check that it is
工程师，所以我必须检查
reasonable performance past performance
过去表现合理
and if not to fix it in any areas I
如果没有解决我在任何地方
didn't tie to particular Java libraries
没有绑定到特定的Java库
concurrent stuff etc whatever needs to
并发的东西等什么需要
management or to customer and this week
管理或客户和本周
I am working on that so okay what we are
我正在为此工作，好吧，我们是什么
talking about a completable future is a
谈论可实现的未来是
very nice class these are very nice
很好的课，这些都很好
features which appears in Java 8
Java 8中出现的功能
unfortunately completable future itself
不幸的是，未来本身可以完成
wasn't used in any other parts of Java 8
没有在Java 8的其他任何部分中使用
just does exist and that's all I'll try
确实存在，这就是我会尝试的全部
to understand how many people around
了解周围有多少人
stars started to using that I did some
星星开始使用我做了一些
short throughway on a twitter asking how
在Twitter上短途询问如何
people are using completable future you
人们正在使用可完成的未来
could see results and I want to ask you
可以看到结果，我想问你
about that
关于那个
first of all please raise your hands who
首先请举手
is using completable future in your code
在您的代码中使用可完成的未来
cool who is just play with that and who
很酷的人，只是和那个玩
do nothing about computable future guys
对可计算的未来家伙什么都不做
I just want to you I'm sorry I won't
我只想要你，对不起，我不会
tell about completable future I am
讲述我的未来
trying to explain performance tricks
试图解释性能技巧
performance syncs how to use it faster
性能同步如何更快地使用它
and I have no time to explain the huge
我没有时间解释
details about computable fish itself but
有关可计算鱼本身的详细信息，但
I hope it'll be and again yet another
我希望这将是又一次
question to that guys who are using
问那些正在使用的家伙
completable future in production please
请在生产中完成未来
who is a satisfied and happy with that
谁对此感到满意和满意
class and who is not okay please come to
上课，谁不好，请来
me after the session all may be in
会议结束后我可能都在
Grenada questions I want to talk I want
格林纳达我想说的问题我想
to collect it back about that stock
收集有关该股票的信息
really you could see that less than half
真的，你可以看到不到一半
of answered people are using completable
的回答者正在使用可完成的
future now I try to understand what's
未来，现在我试图了解什么
happening on github just try to make a
发生在github上只是尝试使
search in completable future and we
寻找可完成的未来，我们
could make conclusions that adoption of
可以得出结论，采用
completed which is not very big but it
完成的不是很大，但是
increases increase in each year what we
每年增加增加我们
have a new in Java 9 first of all I'd
首先，我要在Java 9中有一个新功能
like to say that in Java 9 we already
想说在Java 9中我们已经
have usages of completable future inside
内部具有可完成的未来
our libraries it's such libraries like a
我们的图书馆就像
prototype and the most interesting part
原型和最有趣的部分
is a new HTTP client most of results
是一个新的HTTP客户端，大部分结果
most of performance tips which I will
我将介绍的大多数性能提示
give it's not assumptions that I just
不以为我只是
invented it a practical practical sinks
发明了实用的实用水槽
which were found when I was working on
在我工作时发现的
HTTP to client performance so it's a
HTTP到客户端的性能，这是一个
practical findings maybe I lost some
实际发现也许我失去了一些
ideas but
想法但是
so it just didn't appear on that okay
所以就没出现了
a couple of words about new HTTP client
关于新HTTP客户端的几句话
which appeared in Java nine it's a new
它出现在Java 9中是一个新的
API which should cover boss HTTP 1.1 and
应涵盖老板HTTP 1.1和
HTTP 2 is new API
HTTP 2是新的API
unfortunately this client is not a part
不幸的是，这个客户没有参与
of Java standard yet because of it was a
Java标准，但因为它是一个
lot of discussion and arguing about it
很多讨论和争论
and we decided to put this client into
我们决定将这个客户
incubator incubator is a new feature
孵化器是一个新功能
it's some kind of sandbox where a new
这是一种沙盒，
API will leave for some period of time
API将离开一段时间
and after that we have only two choices
然后我们只有两个选择
you'll have choice change a penance to
您将有选择将a悔改变为
the ties that or we could choose to drop
或者我们可以选择放弃的联系
it drop off completely so 4 gdk9 HTTP
它完全下降，所以4 gdk9 HTTP
client in incubator that is why it's
孵化器中的客户，这就是为什么
quite important for us to get your
对我们来说很重要
feedback and to change and improve that
反馈并进行更改和改进
existing API anyway you could download
仍然可以下载现有的API
gdk9 and play with that I won't tell
gdk9并玩我不会告诉
about HTTP client I just will try to
关于HTTP客户端，我只是会尝试
concentrate it about asynchronous
专注于异步
request because of its a goal of our
请求，因为这是我们的目标
discussion so in the HTTP client we have
讨论，因此在HTTP客户端中
two ways to send request
两种发送请求的方式
it's the synchronous unblocking request
这是同步解锁请求
and asynchronous how they looks like
和异步的样子
synchronous or block in requests looks
同步或阻止请求外观
very simple we are preparing request to
很简单，我们正在准备请求
do in sand and waiting until our HTTP
做沙子，等到我们的HTTP
response arrives we are blocking and
响应到达我们正在阻止，
that invocation of method set after that
之后的方法集调用
we got completely final finished
我们完全完成了
response and could extract all
响应并可以提取所有
information which we need from that and
我们需要的信息，以及
also our plan has a method sank send
我们的计划也有一种沉没的方法
async synchronous in that case we don't
在这种情况下，异步同步
block in that invocation
阻止该调用
we just return completable future of our
我们只是返回我们可完成的未来
aspirants
有抱负的人
and somewhere we could do that future
在某个地方我们可以做那个未来
whatever you want we could just walk on
随便你怎么走
that future to wage results so we could
那个未来要付出结果，所以我们可以
attach the chain of action and process
附加行动和过程链
them so and the other thing which I want
他们是这样，而我想要的另一件事
to emphasize for our HTTP client is a
为我们的HTTP客户端强调的是
ability to set up the executor
建立执行人的能力
so in general we have a lot of a lot of
所以总的来说，我们有很多
options to make a client
成为客户的选择
bla bla bla what what's required to do
bla bla bla bla需要做什么
proper work is HTTP protocol even to
正确的工作是HTTP协议
choose below you could see we are on
选择下面，您可以看到我们在
HTTP to the new standard but as I told
HTTP到新标准，但正如我所说
we are providing two methods blocking
我们提供两种方法阻止
method and asynchronous and if we have a
方法和异步，如果我们有一个
synchronous method we should we should
同步方法，我们应该
somewhere do with that execution because
某处与执行有关，因为
of our original method is not block and
我们原来的方法不是阻塞
in order to provide user its API it's
为了向用户提供其API，
not of a standalone application some
不是一个独立的应用程序
control of our execution we should have
控制我们应该执行的
ability to set up external executor
建立外部执行者的能力
because of and user could narrow or
由于，用户可能会缩小或
expand that area whatever okay what I
扩大那个范围，好吧，我
was think about blocking an asynchronous
在考虑阻止异步
API particularly I will think these two
API，特别是我会认为这两个
kinds of methods the first method which
各种方法第一种方法
is doing something and returning
在做某事并返回
completed result for us and asynchronous
为我们完成的结果和异步
which is doing national moment of
这正在做国家的时刻
invocation and return completable future
调用并返回可完成的未来
I won't talk about different kind of a
我不会谈论另一种
scene who knows providing call bags etc
知道提供通话袋等的场景
it's out of scope of that discussion
这超出了讨论范围
just let's talk about completable future
让我们谈谈可实现的未来
ok the question is do you really need
好吧，问题是您真的需要吗
boss
老板
such methods simultaneously what do you
这样的方法同时你呢
think
认为
but I just want to show you the
但我只想告诉你
following the the one sinkers the
跟随一个沉没
following it's it's very easily with a
跟着它很容易
greased in API to convert I synchronous
在API中润滑以转换I同步
to synchronous on vacation just to do
同步度假只是为了
join on completable future and throws a
加入可完成的未来并抛出
society we could make we could take our
社会，我们可以使我们可以采取我们的
blocking API on pass to the supply ships
传递给补给船时阻塞API
made up of completable fusion will be
由完全融合构成
executed in salmon as a thread and we
在鲑鱼中执行作为线程，我们
will get completable fusion that's
将获得完全的融合
enough so the question is maybe make
足够，所以问题可能是
sense just leave one of the fellas and
感觉就离开一个小伙子，
don't explode our public API let's talk
不要爆炸我们的公共API
about them first of all let's consider
关于他们首先让我们考虑
the first sinks if implementing blocking
如果实施阻塞，第一个会下沉
API just having a synchronous API as the
API仅具有同步API作为
base basic stuff it's the whole three
基本的基本内容是全部三个
lines which we need to make our block in
我们需要在其中插入的行
a pan working will it work yes exactly
平底锅工作会正确吗
it will work but let's see how it will
它会工作，但让我们看看它会如何
work so what we have we have set of
工作，所以我们拥有的是
users threads users that I mean it's
用户线程用户，我的意思是
rate of user environment where we call
我们称呼的用户环境比率
methods of our API and because of what a
API的方法，以及
synchronous there is a some executor
同步有一些执行者
where we should do useful work and we
我们应该在哪里做有用的工作，我们
are doing useful work in an that
在做有用的工作
executor of course such kind of transfer
执行者当然是这种转移
from one state to another and back it
从一种状态到另一种状态并返回
should cost let's just just check how
应该花费我们只是检查一下
how much does it cost
它要多少钱
let's do some execution I did it's
让我们做一些执行，我做到了
relative chart I have some execution 100
相对图表我有一些执行力100
nanosecond useful work 100 microseconds
纳秒有用功100微秒
useful work and 100 milliseconds from
有用的工作和100毫秒
work it's a blue line it is taken by
工作是一条蓝线，由
100% and orange
100％和橙色
it's our overhead of transferring that
这是我们转移的开销
execution to
执行到
yeah and for the first line 100 a second
是的，第一行100秒
I have no place it should be ZZZ these
我没有地方应该是ZZZ这些
orange lines should be passed here here
橙色线应该在这里通过
here there but it's looked like for
在这里，但看起来像
quite a large part of execution with
执行的很大一部分
large box like 100 milliseconds 10
像100毫秒这样的大盒子10
milliseconds even one millisecond it
毫秒甚至一毫秒
doesn't matter how big is acute okay
紧要紧多大都没关系
let's check later
让我们稍后再检查
let's check when I do execution of to
让我们检查一下我何时执行
stress in case of some stations ever hat
在某些电台曾遇到压力的情况下
is increasing and cleanse the execution
正在增加并清理执行
of fosters I know I did a Greek ution on
我知道我对希腊寄养
that particular my laptop which a way of
那个我的笔记本电脑
showing your presentation it's a Lenovo
显示您的演示文稿是联想
ThinkPad blah blah blah
ThinkPad等等等等
it's Casa it has to to your course and
这是Casa，它必须满足您的课程要求，
to hyper thread so we generally have
超线程，所以我们通常有
four Hardware threads for our execution
我们执行的四个硬件线程
and the letter K is letter chart in the
字母K是
situation when our system is situated i
当我们的系统位于
have threads the same amount on more
有更多相同数量的线程
than my hardware allows me to do and in
比我的硬件允许我做的
such situations they ever had of a
他们曾经遇到过这样的情况
synchronous accusin even in case of very
即使在非常情况下
large blocks like 100 milliseconds it's
像100毫秒这样的大块
already quite feasible that is why i
已经很可行了，这就是为什么我
think it's responsible for the first
认为这是第一个原因
question why we need separate
问题，为什么我们需要分开
synchronous employed can appear black an
同步雇用者可能会显得黑
api we need when we have to provide
我们需要提供的api
maximum performance in terms of
最高性能
throughput don't do something in
吞吐量不做任何事情
parallel it will rocks better so okay
平行它会更好地摇摆，好吗
it's somebody also transition form of
它也是某人的过渡形式
execution tasks from one thread to
执行任务从一个线程到
another thread costs so it's quite a
另一个线程的成本，所以这是一个相当
simple idea makes sense to try to avoid
简单的主意可以避免
it
它
ok let's talk about the second way if
好，让我们谈谈第二种方式
you have block in API could be easily to
你在API中有块很容易
create a synchronous a page just by
创建一个同步页面
submitting our tasks continuous threats
提交任务持续不断的威胁
and in this classical way usually we
通常，我们以这种经典方式
have a legacy pair when we already
当我们已经有一对旧的
have a block in a parent we just want to
我们只想在父母中有一个障碍
add a synchronous API
添加一个同步API
will that work let's just change it from
这项工作会改变吗？
our abstraction do something and let's
我们的抽象做点什么，让我们
back to our steep climb in a steep
回到陡峭的山坡上
client it would be looks like this I
客户端，看起来像这样我
have to say that it will works but not
必须说它会工作，但不会
in all cases and I'm sorry we have to
在所有情况下，对不起，我们不得不
spend maybe less 10 minutes to explain
花不到10分钟的时间来解释
why and so two cases when it won't work
为什么，所以两种情况下都行不通
so how typical HTTP request looks like
所以典型的HTTP请求是什么样的
we send header to server will send body
我们发送头到服务器将发送正文
we are waiting header awaiting body it's
我们正在等待标题等待主体
it's very very simply kated picture of
这是非常非常简单的图片
course there are a lot of other details
当然还有很多其他细节
what these receive means it means that
这些收到的意思意味着
we have to wait we have to wait and
我们必须等待我们必须等待
block something okay count of possesses
阻止一些拥有的东西
let's check it how hard work we
让我们检查一下我们有多努力
transferred our execution to digital
将我们的执行转移到数字
thread and we have to the block wait it
线程，我们必须阻止它
could be message wait on object monitor
可能是对象监视器上的消息等待
or it could be measured away it on a
或者可以在一个
condition it could be some kind of
条件可能是某种
blocking cubed ultimatum beneath of
阻止下面的立方体最后通atum
blocking queues there is a wait again
阻塞队列，再次等待
anyway we should stop on some way to
无论如何，我们应该停止某种方式
wait and we will stop execution how a
等待，我们将停止执行
traitor's not working anymore
叛徒不再工作
what we have to do is in that case we we
在这种情况下，我们要做的是
have to execute somewhere the methods
必须在某处执行方法
which will receive response from a
将会收到来自
server and the method which will send
服务器和将发送的方法
notify signal to our great condition and
通知信号我们状况良好，并且
continue execution is that's right I
继续执行是对的，我
have to warn about such scheme which I
必须警告这种计划，我
wrote here don't do that
在这里写不要这样做
why in that key my eyes and receive
为什么在那把钥匙我的眼睛和接收
response in the same executor what does
在同一执行程序中响应
it mean it means in some situation my
这意味着在某些情况下
executor could be blocking all stress
执行者可能会阻止所有压力
and I have no place where to process a
而且我没有地方处理
response and where to wake up so in
反应以及在哪里醒来
reality I need some
现实中我需要一些
and more than just user set executor
不仅仅是用户设置执行器
says I need some amount of oxygen
说我需要一些氧气
Astraeus it could be zero it depends of
阿斯特雷厄斯可能为零
goals it could be a lot of them but for
目标可能很多，但对于
httpclient
httpclient
it's one is enough some kind of folks to
有些人足以
the street which will never block and
永远不会阻塞的街道
which will do proper processing of
这将对
received data and waiting in our stress
收到数据并在压力中等待
which we are waiting results how it
我们正在等待结果如何
works it's the first part of the second
是第二部分的第一部分
part I showed you the meta executor of
我向您展示了
ship client which narrow the usage of my
船运客户，这缩小了我的使用范围
visa cuter allows me to configure the
可爱的签证让我可以配置
system and I think that it's a good idea
系统，我认为这是一个好主意
that if we don't specify some we really
如果我们不指定一些，我们真的
don't put some constraint on that method
不要对该方法施加任何约束
it should allow to our library truck
它应该允许我们的图书馆卡车
with any kind of executor more including
任何种类的执行者，包括
default executors default executors
默认执行者默认执行者
caches thread pool let's think about
缓存线程池让我们考虑一下
little bit about cassia stress pool it
关于决明子压力池的一点点
just copied Javadoc and won't read it
只是复制了Javadoc而不会阅读
aunt emphasizes what a nice think about
阿姨强调了一个很好的想法
caches thread pool it means that if all
缓存线程池，这意味着如果所有
hours rest busier will create new sets
忙碌的小时将创建新的集合
and our new task will be executed cool
我们的新任务将很酷地执行
but the same thing is a negative power
但同样的事情是负面力量
negative things about caching cesspool
有关缓存污水池的负面信息
because of we have to create thread and
因为我们必须创建线程并
thread to the resource it could be
线程可能是资源
expensive let's just do some experiments
昂贵，让我们做一些实验
it's a sound very beginning if you try
如果您尝试的话，这是一个非常好的开始
to implement our HTTP request via simple
通过简单的方式实现我们的HTTP请求
wrapping of existing block in API we
在API中包装现有块
just some moment measured and realized I
只是片刻，我意识到
don't know why but the single HTTP
不知道为什么，但单个HTTP
request general uses 20 threads
请求一般使用20个线程
doesn't mean that 100 simultaneous
并不意味着同时100
requests will required 200 stress any
请求将需要200个压力
ideas other than 200 layers more
除了200层以外的其他想法
yes maybe on the sandwich machine with
是的，也许在三明治机上
configuring and expanding stacks pipe
配置和扩展堆栈管道
spaces etc it will work but I could unit
空间等将工作，但我可以单位
for 100 simoleons requests but someone
为100 simoleons请求，但有人
will get you to 101 requests ok what do
将使您收到101个请求，确定该怎么办
you think how to fix that problem if you
您认为如果您解决该问题
blocked in what innovate thread in our
封锁了我们的创新线索
executor so we have to solve it what we
执行者，所以我们必须解决它
have here we have a send methods which
在这里，我们有一个发送方法
doing a wait and waiting result the idea
做一个等待，等待结果的想法
of how to avoid blocking is quite a
如何避免阻塞相当
simple it's consists of two steps first
简单，它首先包括两个步骤
of all it's very nice things that
最重要的是
completable future could be considered
可以考虑未来的发展
to the condition it's only single-use
只能一次性使用
condition but for God's sake it's the
条件，但为了上帝，这是
same code as before
与以前相同的代码
it's block in the same way as before
与以前相同
because of inside drawing there is a
因为里面有图纸
weight but it's only the first step the
重量，但这只是第一步
second step what we are doing here we
第二步，我们在这里做什么
are trying to perform supply a sink sent
正在尝试执行供应发送的接收器
code and some web block
代码和一些网络阻止
let's inline that and drop into
让我们内联并放入
different set of action in order to
为了采取不同的行动
understand how it works we are making
了解我们正在如何运作
chain and here is the chain way we just
链，这就是我们所使用的链方式
blocking on completable future let's do
阻止可完成的未来吧
this
这个
who all knows what made a design compose
谁知道设计是由什么组成的
Doom does how it works
厄运是如何运作的
nobody's guys there were a lot of hands
没有人有很多手
that you are using completable future
您正在使用可完成的未来
how you could use complain of future
您如何使用抱怨未来
without than compose definitely it's an
毫无疑问，这是一个
almost impossible to do Samson Samson
参孙几乎不可能参孙
interesting without than Campos aye
比坎波斯还有趣
then well then composed on the compose
然后就组成了
is made at which perform lambda function
执行lambda函数的位置
action that action return completable
动作完成的动作
future and then compose return another
将来再撰写返回
computable fusion which is
可计算融合
encapsulate results of our hidden under
封装我们隐藏的结果
our previous complete level fish which
我们以前的完整级别的鱼
were what like a method flat map in a
就像一个方法中的平面图
functional programming but then the most
函数式编程，但是大多数
interesting part she is that if that
她最有趣的部分是
completed of fish is not completed at
鱼未完成的时间
that moment we are not blocking we are
那一刻我们没有阻止我们
just we are not executing our chain of
只是我们没有执行我们的
action here
在这里行动
we just finished which is construction
我们刚完成建设
we are not going to be secured this
我们不会为此得到保证
action here and that means that our
在这里采取行动，这意味着我们
stress will be returned to execute errs
压力将返回来执行错误
if it's read from skilled it means we
如果是从技术人员那里读来的，则意味着我们
did not captures this thread from
没有从捕获该线程
execution that's ready to review do
准备审查的执行情况
something useful its key part of that
一些有用的东西，它的关键部分
sink in reality it's completely
完全陷入现实
eliminated blocking when we use
使用时消除了阻塞
computable fusion making changes Quietus
可计算融合改变Quietus
things nothing so what we have here we
东西什么都没有，所以我们在这里我们
have here our threads we are here we are
在这里有我们的线程我们在这里我们在
doing them compose method there is an
做他们的撰写方法有一个
object's our future and from our oxygen
对象是我们的未来，也是我们的氧气
threat we just send in signal complete
我们只是发送完整的威胁信号
it means that when future became
这意味着当未来变成
completed somewhere maybe another threat
在某个地方完成也许是另一个威胁
we execute subsequent change fractions
我们执行后续的变更分数
and doing what was required that is
并按照要求做
simple results on HTTP client by simple
通过简单的HTTP客户端上的简单结果
emanation of all blockings we got and
我们得到的所有障碍物的产生和
change replacing them to Zen compose you
更改以替换为Zen组成您
got 40% of speed-up of work enemies
提升了40％的工作敌人速度
particular how an you should be client
特别是你应该如何成为客户
and this is blocking elimination is the
而这是消除的障碍
most important things how to make
最重要的事情如何制作
completable future faster it if you are
如果您是未来，可以更快完成
making chain of our confusion
使我们陷入混乱
you shouldn't block if you don't block
如果不阻止，就不应该阻止
our stress or the return
我们的压力或回报
snails and that is quite important the
蜗牛，这是非常重要的
slide is just it's just related to
幻灯片只是与之相关
performance and just for educational
表现，仅用于教育
purposes moment then compose I thought
目的时刻然后组成我以为
it's the most interesting method in the
这是最有趣的方法
calculate above huge actors this example
计算以上巨大的演员这个例子
show you how to make infinite recursive
向您展示如何进行无限递归
chain of completable fusion if you want
如果需要，可完成融合链
only with that we could do this Oh as
只有这样我们才能做到这一点
adjust does Google guys it's very
调整谷歌家伙，这是非常
amazing stuff ok let's move further
好东西，让我们进一步
before we will continue our talk I just
在我们继续讨论之前，我只是
want to ask you the following question
想问你以下问题
let's imagine I have two strands and
假设我有两条线
from ones that I'm doing future complete
从我将来要做的那些
and from other straight I am attaching
从其他直系我附上
chain affection which thread will give
哪条线会给人以感情
you to our action who will vote for for
您采取我们的行动，谁将投票支持
case a b c d r how we could educated for
案例abcdr我们如何接受教育
that correct answers that it could be
可能是正确的答案
executed either from set one or either
从一组或任一组执行
from so true and also that is quite
从如此真实，这也是相当
important point where the chain of
重点链
computable future will be executed for
可计算的未来将被执行
processing and without understanding
加工且不了解
that we can't talk about complain about
我们不能谈论抱怨
future performance it's just some
未来的表现只是一些
summary I will later I will show
摘要，稍后我将展示
examples but here a little bit summaries
例子，但这里有一些总结
I just saying is that if we are using
我只是说，如果我们使用
methods then apply then compose etcetera
然后应用方法然后撰写等
the this action could be executed
这个动作可以执行
anywhere it can be executed from a
可以从任何地方执行
threat which perform completion of our
威胁完成我们的
future it could be executed from chain
将来可以从链中执行
construction in places where we are
在我们所处的地方建造
constructing our chain or even it could
构建我们的链，甚至可以
be written from a place when we call get
当我们打电话给get的时候写
join users here I want to show you a
在这里加入用户，我想给你看一个
couple several examples which I did
几个我做了的例子
using distress
用苦恼
it's some such tools which were done
这是一些这样的工具
sometimes for analyzing tasting some
有时用于分析品尝
concurrency G tricks inside inside GDK
GDK内部的并发G技巧
side job it's the first example little
副业，这是第一个例子
bit about notation above its
关于符号的一点点
precondition it's that performed before
前提条件是之前执行过
we executed our threads on the left side
我们在左侧执行了线程
that's one threat on the right side it's
那是右边的一个威胁
not a straight they executed
他们执行的不是直线
simultaneously a lot of a lot of type
同时很多很多类型
times to get to capture all kinds of
是时候捕捉各种
races huge we could get first example
比赛规模巨大，我们可以得到第一个榜样
from one threat we are doing complete
从一个威胁，我们正在完成
from another state we are doing shank
从另一个州我们正在做小腿
instructions below you could see results
以下说明可以看到结果
it's an exact number of that execution a
这是执行的确切数量
lot of action inside construction said a
建筑内部很多动作说
lot of lock action inside completion
完成内部有很多锁定动作
strength another example what will
实力再举一个例子
happen if you do future complete from
如果您将来完成的话会发生
two threads who know what's return type
两个知道返回类型的线程
of future complete return type of future
未来的完整回报类型
complete method is boolean could you
完整的方法是布尔值可以吗
guess what does it mean what know
猜猜这是什么意思
yes mail complete reasons true if that
是邮件完整的原因为
invocation completed future or return
调用完成的将来或返回
false if that location failed to
如果该位置失败，则返回false
complete future because of it could be
完整的未来，因为它可能是
race okay let's make an action and make
比赛好吧，让我们采取行动，
an action before trying company it's
尝试与公司合作之前的行动
just future action and I to the
只是未来的行动，而我
completion from two strands
两股完成
before I wrote that that test I was
在我写那个测试之前，我是
thinking that it was a journalism action
认为这是新闻行动
should be from successfully completion
应该从成功完成
thread but it's not a true it also could
线程，但这不是真的，它也可以
be executed from another thread which
从另一个线程执行
failed to complete okay there was a
未能完成好吗？
second example we are just doing one
第二个例子，我们只是做一个
complete and one join just getting
完成并加入一个联接
results from our future and the same
来自我们未来的结果
that action could be executed from both
该动作可以从两个执行
stress due to the rains nature of the
由于下雨天的压力
threat and the last example because try
威胁和最后一个例子，因为尝试
to be questa when I have a future and
当我有未来的时候成为疑问
two action it's parallel independent
两个动作是并行独立的
action I just attached like two chains
我像两条链子一样附加的动作
and from our one straight I'm doing
从一开始我就在做
complete from another straight time to
从另一个时间完成
enjoy and again both of my action could
再次享受我的行动
be executed from the single thread or
从单线程执行或
both of my action could be executed in
我的两个动作都可以在
different and it's an issue so why we
不同，这是一个问题，所以为什么我们
have such where's the behavior in
有这样的行为在哪里
reality all methods in computer we know
现实中我们知道的所有计算机方法
future has several forms like then apply
未来有几种形式，然后适用
and corresponding methods then applies
然后采用相应的方法
in query we could specify particular
在查询中，我们可以指定特定
executor where we want to be our action
我们想成为我们行动的执行者
for execution why we definitely needed
为了执行我们为什么绝对需要
and to get an answer for SATA and trying
并获得SATA的答案并尝试
suggestion to compare performance of
建议比较性能
that I have a simple chain of two
我有两个简单的链
actions not a lot of and one chain is
动作不多，一个链条是
doing then apply it means that we don't
然后应用它意味着我们不
have additional submission for executors
有额外的提交给执行者
each time and the knowledge in a supply
每次和供应中的知识
Synchron
同步处理
action zipper separately submitted to
动作拉链分别提交给
execute in here the performance also
在这里执行表演
because of very different numbers I'm
因为数字差异很大
showing only relative differences for
仅显示的相对差异
small tasks so a difference quite
小任务，所以差异很大
visible for large tasks maybe doesn't
对于大型任务可见，也许不
matter for our transition but again it
对于我们的过渡很重要，但再次
still exists until our system is
直到我们的系统
saturated when they have a lot of
当他们有很多饱和
threads the difference between the
线程之间的差异
single thread chain and Martin guitar
单线链和马丁吉他
chains could be different so the
链条可能会有所不同，因此
conclusion is simple we have to form of
结论很简单，我们必须形成
methods n Samson Samson I think by two
方法n Samson Samson我认为有两个
reasons a sink gives predictability you
接收器可预测的原因
have control way to execute your code
有控制方式来执行您的代码
but then something gives performance way
但随后有一些表现方式
not to go back' and also it just the
不回去”，也只是
same about transition or execution from
相同的过渡或执行
one thread to another
一个线程到另一个
why we need predictability there is a
为什么我们需要可预测性
simple example particularly from the
简单的例子，特别是来自
same way as our HTTP client we have only
与我们的HTTP客户端相同的方式
one single aux fleurs ready
准备好一个辅助助手
it's called selector manager it just
它叫做选择器管理器
really sleeping on new selector getting
真的在新选择器上睡觉
notification read data from network and
通知从网络读取数据并
dispatch data to particular receivers
将数据分发给特定的接收者
very simple okay how it works in the
非常简单，知道它如何在
situation we have a future and we have
情况，我们有未来，我们有
set of actions action foo is action
动作集动作foo是动作
which change to a future inside our
改变我们内心的未来
executor thorough internal action but
遗嘱执行人彻底的内部行动，但
after that we return our future to user
之后，我们将未来归还给用户
and a user could attach any kind of
用户可以附加任何种类的
action to confusion its idea to of
混淆其思想的行动
completed future to chain actions so we
完成了连锁行动的未来，所以我们
have chains of actions if you are doing
有一系列的行动，如果你在做
complete from a selector what does it
从选择器完成是什么
mean it means that we could boss actions
意味着我们可以领导行动
foo and bar execute from that particular
foo和bar从该特定位置执行
selector manager why we should not do
选择器经理为什么我们不应该做
that because of you don't know how much
因为你不知道多少
time
时间
Foom okay you could know about Excel
Foom好的，您可能了解Excel
fool you could measure you could do it
傻瓜，你可以衡量，你可以做到
you could write but you don't know
你可以写，但你不知道
anything about action bar and it could
关于动作栏的任何事情，它都可以
be any kind of dos attack for your
对您来说是任何一种dos攻击
system we have one important very
系统我们有一个非常重要的
important beeps read and you do a lot of
阅读重要的哔声，您会做很多事情
action here
在这里行动
that's right won't read anything from
没错，不会读取任何内容
Network dispatch as a request and all
网络调度作为请求和全部
activity who stop so you can't do that
活动停止了，所以你不能那样做
you need predictability you should avoid
您需要可预测性，应该避免
such kind of education here we just
这样的教育，我们只是
can't from executors read make them
不能从执行者那里读到使他们
compose some actions and here's a make
作一些动作，这是一个使
completion of our action what happened
我们行动的完成发生了什么
oh there are several ways to solve that
哦，有几种方法可以解决这个问题
problem first of all in Java nine we got
问题首先在Java九中
a new methods which absent in Java 8
Java 8中缺少的新方法
which called complete I think it means
我认为这意味着完成
that we won't execute anything from our
我们将不会执行任何事情
selector menus latent will complete
潜在的选择器菜单将完成
execution to us available straight in
直接执行给我们
executors nice the same way to solving
执行者很好的解决方法
the problem in and Chara eight we are
问题和Chara八我们
doing complete here but we know and by
在这里完成，但是我们知道
using design compose sync we protected
使用我们保护的设计撰写同步
our select managers right that's nice it
我们的精选经理人很好
works right now you got really working
现在可以正常工作了
solution but it costs and it caused that
解决方案，但这会导致成本增加
if we are have for example already
如果我们已经有例如
completed fusion making them compose we
完成融合使他们组成了我们
are making them compose as sync and we
使他们组成同步，我们
are doing it from a one executor said we
是由一位执行人说的
have the same problem we be very
有同样的问题，我们非常
frequently doing transferring tasks from
经常从
one is in theatres and the cuter trap
一个在剧院和可爱的陷阱
and that is useless activity maybe we
那是无用的活动，也许我们
could unit somehow it's a quite simple
可以以某种方式组合起来，这很简单
trick let's check it if our future done
让我们检查一下，如果我们的未来完成了
or not done before
还是以前没做过
and if our future are done let's do them
如果我们的未来完成了，那就去做
Campos and in that case will be executed
坎波斯，在这种情况下将被处决
directly in that top point from the same
直接在同一点的最高点
thread without any issues if our future
线程，如果我们的未来没有任何问题
is not completed yet ok
还没有完成还可以
say if we have to move into executors
说我们是否必须进入执行者
and provide such kind of protections of
并提供以下保护
the identity function with a sync option
带有同步选项的身份功能
to move it in the executor and that tree
在执行器和那棵树中移动它
could not tip that is the tree a tree
不能提示那棵树是一棵树
but that give for us 16 percent of
但这给了我们百分之十六
execution time for our HTTP client it's
我们的HTTP客户端的执行时间是
it's quite a nice result just just just
这只是一个不错的结果
change just just write three lines of
改变只是写三行
code to get sixteen to send you really
的代码，以获得十六个真正发送给您的代码
can do that and yet another trick I know
可以做到，而我知道另一个技巧
we have the following chains of action
我们有以下行动链
to our completable fusions like King
像金这样的完整融合
inside of medicine nursing and methods
内科护理方法
and AIESEC is called from user start and
从用户开始调用AIESEC并
we are expecting that it will make all
我们期望它将使所有
details return completable future almost
细节回报即将完成的未来
immediately
立即
our API because of it should basically
我们的API，因为它应该基本上
on practice it realized I checked that I
在实践中它意识到我检查了我
did some measurement and realized that
做一些测量，意识到
in very rare cases only 3% of requests
在极少数情况下，只有3％的请求
but in 3 percent of requests when we
但是在3％的请求中
passed the last composed actions we
通过了我们最后的动作
already have a completed future because
已经有一个完整的未来，因为
of server respond for us we got results
服务器响应我们，我们得到了结果
but we have to do some some other
但是我们必须做一些其他的事情
results and process like but getting bad
结果和过程像但变坏了
etc cetera if we have for such chain we
等等等等，如果我们有这样的连锁店，我们
have already completed future it means
已经完成了未来，这意味着
that the last chain the tail of chain
那最后一条链条的尾巴
actions will be executed from user
动作将由用户执行
thread we transfer but we wanted
线程，我们转移，但我们想要
everything transfer to executor strength
一切转移到执行者的力量
not do it from users okay we could use
不要从用户那里做，我们可以使用
then compose I think as I told you
然后按照我告诉你的方式思考
thread will be protected we will not
线程将受到保护，我们不会
doing something but again the same
做某事，但还是一样
station
站
unnecessary switching when we don't want
当我们不想的时候不必要的切换
how to solve that problem it's
如何解决这个问题
the simple idea let's do chain of
简单的想法，让我们做
execution just make a complete ball
执行只是使一个完整的球
incomplete futures beginning make the
不完整的期货开始使
whole food chain of our completable
我们完整的整个食物链
fusions full chain of actions which we
融合了我们完整的行动链
need to do and only one our chin is
需要做的，只有我们的下巴
ready to trigger the cue ssin just
准备触发提示球
sending the matter complete a sink and
将此事发送完整
providing middle voice really with no
提供中间声音真的没有
will be enough it enough triggers to
足以触发
diffuse the whole chain and delayed
扩散整个链并延迟
start give us some practical examples
开始给我们一些实际的例子
plus 10% two synchros request any
再加上10％的两个同步请求
questions
问题
it's quite a simple I have huge I don't
这很简单我有很多我没有
need the result so I could make a
需要结果，所以我可以做一个
computable future void complete about
可计算的未来空缺完整
fusion avoid what's complete about
融合避免什么是完整的
difference between complete stable
完全稳定之间的差异
future of wood and completable future of
木材的未来和可替代的未来
boolean who could guess how many states
谁能猜出多少个州的布尔值
a happen completable future boolean and
发生可完成的未来布尔值和
completely future void what
完全没有未来
for complete o future of boolean I have
为了布尔的完整未来
States complete normally this true
国家通常会完成这件事
complete normal use false incomplete and
完全正常使用错误不完全和
complete with exception for void I have
完成我有空的例外
less debt I have incomplete complete
少欠我不完整的债务
with exception and complete because of I
由于我而异常而完整
have no any other values for where it's
没有其他任何值
then no but I just want to have complete
那不行，但我只想完成
or incomplete future need details here I
或未来的需求不完整，请在这里
could use any kind of type here but void
可以在这里使用任何类型但无效
is minimal enough and the last and lyin'
足够小，最后一个和'
lyin' I'd just triggers execution
lyin'我只是触发执行
because of I completing my future and
因为我完成了我的未来，
there is in start running before that my
在那之前我已经开始运行了
chain is protected because of the
链受到保护，因为
topmost future want to be executed I
最重要的未来我想被执行
just constructions chain and and just a
只是建筑链，而只是
simple simple trick gives me ten percent
简单简单的把戏给了我百分之十
real HTTP requests examples yes yes
真实的HTTP请求示例是是
because of the KD of all I synchronous
因为所有我同步的KD
requests for completable fuchsia is not
要求完成紫红色
about completable future
关于可完成的未来
it's about threads the threads is our
关于线程，线程是我们的
key resource we don't need a lot of
关键资源，我们不需要很多
threads and we don't need a few months
线程，我们不需要几个月
we need a right amount of stress usually
我们通常需要适量的压力
comparable with this amount of course on
可以与这个课程相当
our machine or somehow else limited by
我们的机器或其他方式受
our environment and we have to avoid
我们的环境，我们必须避免
unnecessary stress we have to avoid
我们必须避免不必要的压力
inefficient amount
无效量
and we have to avoid unnecessary
而且我们必须避免不必要的
transition from one server to another
从一台服务器过渡到另一台服务器
that's all and if we delay the start of
就这样，如果我们延迟启动
always if usually wheels just making for
通常如果车轮只是为了
us better understanding where my actions
我们更好地了解我的行为
will be executed to avoid all kind of
将被执行以避免各种
races and just do it and select the last
比赛，然后选择最后一个
trick which I want to show you it's not
我想告诉你的把戏不是
related to complete the fish itself but
与完成鱼本身有关，但
I can't hide it at should know as I told
我告诉我，我不能将其隐藏
the default executors for our ship plan
我们船舶计划的默认执行人
is cached at pool is that a really good
缓存在游泳池是一个非常好的
choice why no no all after all fixes I
选择为什么没有全部解决办法
did a lot of execution it didn't grow
做了很多执行却没有增长
more than 100 strats anything what what
超过100个阶层
i doing
我在做
except of user action of course which
当然除了用户动作
could block but it's it's you submitting
可以阻止，但这是您提交的
the actions but the problem is that as i
行动，但问题是，因为我
told it's not really the best read the
告诉我这不是最好的阅读
best executor for HTTP request i didn't
我没有HTTP请求的最佳执行程序
try to do something unethical and cetera
尝试做一些不道德的事
I just did practical evaluation because
我只是做了实际的评估，因为
of I have a benchmark I could different
我有一个基准，我可能会有所不同
executors and check how it works and for
执行者并检查其工作方式以及
particular HTTP to protocol fix its
特定的HTTP协议修复
report the cuter with just two three at
仅用2个三点报告可爱
maximum gives me the best results lately
最近，max给我最好的结果
it's easy for me to explain that because
我很容易解释一下，因为
of I know how the ship it works it
我知道船是如何运作的
limited to write Internet or colita me
仅限写互联网或给我打电话
because it's sequential part of which
因为它是其中的顺序部分
hardly to paralyze it limited to whistle
几乎不让它瘫痪
encoding because the cell encoding also
编码，因为单元格编码也
hard to paralyze that is why I to stress
很难瘫痪，这就是为什么我要强调
as more than enough to get the fastest
足以获得最快的速度
but the right tools of the future could
但是未来的正确工具可以
give you a huge difference of I think
我想给你带来很大的不同
incipient you should check it for your
初期您应该检查一下
application ok a little bit conclusion
应用还可以一点结论
we were talking about completable huge
我们在谈论可完成的巨大
performance and I definitely asking guys
表演，我肯定会问大家
where what's the problem what you'd like
问题出在哪里
or don't like incomplete no future and
或不喜欢不完整的未来
such kind of complaint I am getting for
我要抱怨的事
many many times
很多很多次
everybody told me that completable
每个人都告诉我
future has particular completion stage
未来有特定的完成阶段
as a key interface of computable which
作为可计算的关键接口
has a very difficult phase a lot of
有一个非常困难的阶段
methods hard to remember we have four
难以记住的方法，我们有四种
minutes remaining and I hope in last few
剩下的几分钟，我希望能在最后几分钟
means I will show you how to speed up
就是说我会告诉你如何加速
not computable future but to the Java
不是可计算的未来，而是Java
developer okay completion stage it has
开发人员可以完成的阶段
exactly 38 methods and 36 from this 38
恰好有38种方法，而这38种方法中有36种
it's a duplicated method in three forms
这是三种形式的重复方法
something a sync with the explicit
与显式同步
executor something async without its
执行器没有它的异步
final executor and that sums let's check
最后的执行者，总和让我们检查一下
Samson I think it means that that
参孙，我认为这意味着
actions we should be submitting here we
我们应该在此处提交的操作
are given and that invocation will be
被给予，调用将是
passed to that Spitfire to execute that
传递给那个烈性人执行
action all subsequent change its I show
行动所有后续更改其显示
an example it's quite important for
一个例子，对于
predictability
可预测性
the second method it's the same as
第二种方法与
before just we are using a fork join
在我们使用派生联接之前
pool as an executor means NASA and the
作为执行人的池意味着NASA和
short method that means that if future
简短的方法意味着如果将来
is complete we will execute action in
完成后，我们将在
place if not complete that will be
如果不完整的地方将是
diluted from other situation which is
从其他情况稀释
much more difficult combination so as a
更加困难的组合
top 36 method has three forms what it
前36种方法有三种形式
means it means we have only 12 methods
表示我们只有12种方法
for understanding transactions now in
了解现在的交易
from these 12 method could be separated
从这12种方法中可以分开
and three forms apply except trap also
三种形式适用，但陷阱也适用
they have completely the similar
他们完全相似
behavior the difference is a polar apply
行为差异是极地适用
is taking results from a previous future
正在从以前的未来取得成果
and I think new results for subsequent
我认为接下来的新结果
future accept just getting
未来接受只是得到
results from a future giving it to
未来给予它的结果
consumer no more results and final
消费者再也没有结果
computable future has a type words as
可计算的未来的类型为
shown for us that execution is finished
向我们表明执行已完成
when that completable future completed
那可完成的未来何时完成
this means that our occasion is finished
这意味着我们的场合已经结束
and run again we don't take any results
再跑一次，我们没有任何结果
you don't prop from previous execution
你不支持以前的执行
we don't provide any results to
我们没有提供任何结果
subsequent change of the question we
问题的后续变化我们
just execute runnable and these nine
只需执行可运行，这九个
methods it's quite a simple so we have a
方法非常简单，所以我们有一个
simple in consent applies and accepts
简单同意即适用并接受
around we have a binary or operational
周围我们有一个二进制或可操作的
in binary and operations when we have it
在二进制和操作中，当我们拥有它
in or we started our chain when Isis is
或我们在伊希斯（Isis）
in port aliza this input is ready in
在阿里扎港，此输入已准备就绪
binary and operation as usual we're
二进制和常规操作
waiting when boss results are ready for
等待老板结果准备好
us it's quite simple with these two nine
我们这两个九很简单
methods we have three metres for
我们有三米的方法
exploration which means methods and
探索意味着方法和
again you should forget that all matters
再一次，你应该忘记所有的事情
before half-alien without some new visa
在没有任何新签证的半外国人之前
sink and I think version we have another
下沉，我认为我们有另一个版本
the methods ramirez then Campos handle
拉米雷斯然后坎波斯处理的方法
and when complete I already told you a
完成后，我已经告诉过您
little bit about and Campos you could
一点点和坎波斯，你可以
read something about that late of
读一些有关
understanding how to do is that there
知道该怎么办
are a lot of interesting blogs around
周围有很多有趣的博客
the stuff probably I have to add links
这些东西可能我必须添加链接
I'll do it maybe later and handle handle
我可能稍后再处理
it's a method which works not only we is
这是一种方法，不仅我们
normally completed future but at me is
通常完成的未来，但对我来说
exceptionally complete description we
非常完整的描述，我们
just taking results or exceptions as to
只是采取结果或例外
pair of arguments pass it to a function
一对参数将其传递给函数
and provide new results and when
并提供新结果以及何时
complete it's the same as handle it's
完成与处理相同
accept version of handle we are taking
接受我们正在使用的手柄版本
result so exception but it doesn't
结果如此异常，但事实并非如此
matter which result will provide the
哪个结果将提供
results of males when complete will be
男性完成的结果将是
the same as region that's all employers
和所有雇主一样的地区
are 2 menno's with which don't have
有2个没有的Menno
a sink form as exceptionally which
下沉形式异常
allows to convert exceptionally
允许异常转换
completed future to normally complete
完成，将来正常完成
the future with some results and method
未来的一些结果和方法
converts completion state to complete my
转换完成状态以完成我的
future from my point of view that's all
从我的角度来看，这就是全部
it's not so difficult to remember all
记住所有内容并不难
methods from completion stage to work
从完成阶段到工作的方法
result okay
结果还好
I'm sinking of out of time so do you
我没时间了，你呢
have any questions
有任何疑问
[Applause]
[掌声]